

•

+91-8606926505



ashiksalim93@gmail.com



Manjamala - Thachappally Temple Road, Keezhthonnakkal, 695313, India

SKILLS

FRP

TALLY

MS-Office (Word/Excel/PowerPoint)

Payroll administration

Languages : English/Hindi/Malayalam

Time management

Handling pressure

Corporate Accounting

VAT return

Financial Auditing

Expert in customer relations

Multi-Task Management

Accounts Payable/Receivable

Ashik Salim

ACCOUNTANT

ABOUT ME

I am seeking a challenging position in your organization to effectively use my knowledge and skills. My Technical and professional business career exhibits a record of strong achievements and significant contributions. The enclosed resume details my experience and accomplishments. Throughout my career, I have been known as a quick learner and a self-starter. I have demonstrated my ability to handle a variety of tasks effectively.

I have 6 Years' experience in Accounts & Purchase and I got very good experience in accounts up to Finalization. I have working knowledge in various accounting packages like Tally, ERP and other customized Packages etc.

Please contact me if my qualifications and skills will match with your current opening in order to further discuss my background. I am ready to put all my sincere efforts and skills to bring the best results for the growth of your organization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accountant

ARAB UNITY SCHOOL, DUBAI / Oct 2016 - Jul 2020

Duties & Responsibilities: -

Daily Basis:-

- Handling bank transactions and monitoring of daily bank Position.
- Preparation of daily cash, cheque and POS card collection report.
- Preparation, allocation and posting of Receipt (bank/Cash) Vouchers.
- Verify payment vouchers and posting.
- Payment to Supplier after verification of all supporting documents.
- ¬ Petty cash handling, Posting of all Payments (ie. Bank, Cash, Petty cash voucher etc.)
- Preparation of Debit note and Credit Note and posting
- Daily Report of Bank balance, LC, Guarantees etc.
- Processing payment of Suppliers/Subcontractors.
- Preparation of Journal Vouchers and Posting.

Month end Report: -

- Preparing staff salary.
- Maintaining student account and ensuring payments are collecting on the due date
- Monthly reconciliation of Trade Receivable/Payable
- Keep track of PDC (Bills Payable)
- Monthly Bank Reconciliation of 2 banks.
- ¬ Preparation of Salary Statement
- Maintaining Staff's Ledger account
- Monthly collection and payment report
- Passing Adjustment entries like outstanding/ prepaid exp., depreciation etc.
- Finalization of Trial balance, P/L & Balance sheet
- ¬ Other report required by the management
- Assisting Finance Manager Reporting day to day activities related to Accounts.

Accounts Assistant

SAM Building contracting LLC, Dubai. / Feb 2014 - Aug 2016

Duties & Responsibilities: -

- Verifying all Purchase Invoice and Posting in Tally
- Preparation of progressive Payment Certificate of Sub-contractors.
- Preparation of LPO.
- Preparation, allocation and posting of Receipt (bank/Cash) Vouchers.
- ¬ Verify Sales voucher and Posting
- Preparing cheque for Supplier after verification of all supporting documents.
- Petty cash handling, Posting of all Payments (ie. Bank, Cash, Petty cash voucher etc.)
- ¬ Daily Payment Report.
- Processing payment of Suppliers/Subcontractors.
- Preparation of Journal Vouchers and Posting.

Purchasing Assistant

DIANBY SHOE WORLD, TRIVANDRUM

Duties & Responsibilities:-

- Monitor stock levels and identify purchasing needs
- Research potential vendors.
- Track orders and ensure timely delivery Daily Payment Report.
- **=** Evaluate offers from vendors and negotiate better prices
- Follow up with suppliers, as needed, to confirm or change orders
- Liaise with warehouse staff to ensure all products arrive in good condition

EDUCATION

MBA

Jaipur National University / 2020

MBA (Finance) 2018-2020

B.COM

Kerala University / 2013

B.COM (Finance with computer application) 2010-2013